ITA's BitVector Genealogy Puzzle

Problem posted at:
http://www.itasoftware.com/careers/puzzle_archive.html

(Long-Winded) Explanation can be found at:

https://docs.google.com/document/d/1YNM9sLNCdC-7w0MqPxut_Qqqp9pu-5lkmHeXhp1GOgs/edit?usp=sharing

I've only seen a half-dozen people online who have tried to solve this puzzle, so I'm not sure if there's anyone still Googling for different approaches to this problem, but I thought I'd add my solution to the
mix.

It's a bit different from the other solutions I've seen online in terms of strategy, and the Google Doc I've attached with a decent explanation of the math behind it.